Roxy Harriette Grove papers, Inclusive: 1906-1953, undated, Bulk: 1930-1949, undated
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- Oversize, 1912 August, 1918 May, undated; 3
  - "The Wood Fire", undated (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 9)
  - "The Wood Fire," full score, undated (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 10)
  - "Dawn," and "Prayer", undated (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 11)
  - "Dawn", undated (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 12)
  - "Dawn", undated (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 13)
  - "Saskatchewan" - Voices, undated (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 14)
  - "Saskatchewan", undated (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 15)
  - "Berceuse", 1918 March 18 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 16)
  - "Corale in E Minor", undated (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 17)
  - "Corale in G Major-In Dulce Jubilo", undated (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 18)
  - "A Childs Series" to Hugh Lowe Grove, Jr., undated (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 19)
  - "Prayer", undated (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 20)
  - "Untitled", 1912 August (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 21)
  - "Schubert - Soirees de Vienne", undated (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 22)
  - "Choral in B Minor", undated (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 23)
  - Print of John Phillip Sousa, undated (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 24)
  - Unidentified Portrait, undated (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 25)